【The fate that cannot be liberated】
【无法解脱的命运】
[Episode 6]
[第6集]
Miss He, what are you doing here?
何小姐，你来这里做什么？
I heard that you are going to Hanshan Temple.
听说你要去寒山寺。
I came to say goodbye
我是来告别的
Then say goodbye, just the two of us.
然后说再见，只有我们两个人。
Maybe in the future,
也许在将来，
We can still be friends.
我们仍然可以成为朋友。
Not allowed?
不允许？
friends?
朋友们？
all good.
都好。
Sir, what would you like to eat?
先生，您想吃什么？
I want roast pork
我要烤猪肉
Please add some ginger , not onions.
请加点生姜 ，不要加洋葱。
Cook some food and bring some wine.
炒点菜，带点酒。
he's good.
他很好。
- Look at that gentleman. - I want to do something cool
- 看看那位先生。 - 我想做一些很酷的事情
But we have to manage here.
但我们必须在这里进行管理。
He is so handsome.
他太帅了。
What are you looking at? Have you never seen a beautiful person before?
你在看什么？ 以前没见过漂亮的人吗？
We are not looking there.
我们没有在那儿寻找。
I didn't say you were beautiful. I'm talking about myself.
我没有说你很漂亮。 我说的是我自己。
That's why I don't want them to look at me.
这就是为什么我不想让他们看我。
You are very patient.
你很有耐心。
How can you eat peanuts so elegantly?
吃花生怎么可以 这么优雅？
For these things,
对于这些事情，
I'm too lazy to peel it off
我都懒得剥了
Give me your hand.
把你的手给我。
you...
你...
When we were in Shangzhou,
我们在商州的时候，
One night, a bag of chestnuts was given.
一天晚上， 送了一袋栗子。
Did you peel it off?
是你剥的吗？
Rong Yu,
Rong Yu,
You are indeed a good person.
你确实是一个好人。
You help me and protect me.
你帮助我并保护我。
but i did it
但我做到了
So much to embarrass him.
这么多让他难堪。
today,
今天，
I sincerely want to ask
我真诚地想问
sorry.
对不起。
If we want to discuss who is right and who is wrong
如果我们要讨论谁对谁错
It seems this is my fault.
看来这是我的错。
So let’s forgive ourselves.
所以，让我们原谅自己吧。
It would be nice if you could forgive me.
如果你能原谅我就好了。
As the young master of Xingxiang Pavilion,
作为星象阁的少主，
trapped in the pavilion
被困在亭子里
I can see stars every day
每天都能看到星星
It must be boring, right?
一定很无聊吧？
Contrary to what Miss He thought,
与何小姐的想法相反，
He and I find astrology interesting.
他，我觉得占星学 很有趣。
everyone's destiny
每个人的命运
Written on the vast starry sky.
写在浩瀚的星空上。
Some are simple at first glance
有些乍一看很简单
Others are twisty and complex.
其他的则曲折而复杂。
Whether sad or happy,
无论悲伤还是快乐，
I can live on anything.
我可以靠任何东西生活。
My body sits in the yard
我的身体坐在院子里
But it seems like I passed
但好像我通过了
Countless reincarnations.
无数的轮回。
like what?
像什么？
I will tell
我会告诉
The story of the late emperor.
已故皇帝的故事。
The life of the late emperor?
先帝的一生？
Can we talk about The Secret History of the Palace?
我们能谈谈 皇宫秘史吗？
Romantic feelings are not an issue.
浪漫的感情不是问题。
Well, when I was grounded.
好吧，当我被禁足时。
you feel bad
你感觉不好
for a while.
一阵子。
I do not want to eat
我不想吃饭
Nor playing with anything.
也不玩任何东西。
Thanks for a romance
感谢一场浪漫
This keeps me strong.
这让我保持坚强。
Romantic feelings are also talked about .
还谈到 了浪漫的感情。
But people didn't invent anything.
但人们并没有发明任何东西。
My copy appears to be the only one left.
我的副本似乎是唯一剩下的一份。
look. I carry it with me all the time.
看。我一直随身携带它。
If you like it, it will definitely produce more.
如果你喜欢它， 它肯定会产生更多。
I hope so.
但愿如此。
Won't you tell the story of the late emperor?
你不讲一下 先帝的故事吗？
Come.
来。
Thanks to the predictions of astrology,
感谢占星术的预言，
The emperor married a woman he did not love.
皇帝娶了 一个他不爱的女人。
Still the person he truly loved
依然是他真心爱过的人
Because of him, he became Jia Lin’s hostage.
因为他而成为家琳的人质，
hope she can
希望她能
Stay with the late emperor.
留在已故皇帝身边。
After going through many difficulties,
在经历了重重困难之后，
at the end,
在最后，
She had to jump into the river and die.
她不得不跳进河里死掉。
The late emperor spent the rest of his life in regret.
而先帝则 在遗憾中度过了余生。
what is that? Is this a ghost story?
那是什么？ 这是鬼故事吗？
Why is Xingxiang Pavilion so evil?
星象阁为何如此邪恶？
The girl destined to become the Phoenix is ​​the queen that everyone wants.
注定要成为凤凰的女孩，就是 所有人都想要的皇后。
Xingxiang Pavilion just fulfilled its duty.
星象阁 只是尽到了自己的职责。
no matter how many times
无论多少次
Looking back on the late emperor’s star,
回首忆 先帝星，
The result is still the same.
结果还是一样。
I do not like it.
我不喜欢它。
Although I shouldn't have said it
虽然我不应该说出来
I still want to say.
我还想说。
The late emperor was very irresponsible.
已故皇帝 非常不负责任。
Sorry to keep you waiting.
对不起，让你久等了。
enjoy.
享受。
are you drinking?
你在喝酒吗？
It wouldn't be a farewell without some wine.
没有酒就不算告别。
But last time he was drunk.
但上次他喝醉了。
We don't need to drink so much this time.
这次我们不需要喝那么多了。
One bowl is enough.
一碗就够了。
Would you like to have a drink with me?
你愿意和我一起喝一碗吗？
Do you want me to drink?
你要我喝吗？
he's good.
他很好。
Wait a moment.
等一下。
I... I still have something to say.
我…… 我还有话要说。
Rong Yu.
Rong Yu.
I just apologized to you,
刚才 我只是向你道歉，
But I didn't thank you.
但我没有感谢你。
Thank you for your continued help and protection.
感谢您一直以来对我的帮助和保护。
Meeting you is the greatest luck in my life, but He Jiuling is insulting me.
遇见你是我这辈子最大的幸运， 而贺九菱却在辱骂我。
Next time we meet,
下次我们见面时，
Things will never be the same again.
事情将不再一样。
I'm not good with words.
我不善言辞。
Hope your trip to Hanshan Temple
希望您的寒山寺之旅
it will be peaceful
它将是和平的
And filled with joy.
并充满喜悦。
Today is the Lantern Festival,
今天是元宵节，
So let's have fun.
所以让我们玩得开心吧。
let's go.
我们走吧。
There won't be another chance again.
以后不会再有别的机会了。
♫ It’s when the sun sets in the evening♫
♫ 就是黄昏夕阳西下的时候 ♫
♫I traveled thousands of miles♫
♫我旅行千里之外♫
♫ Play the sitar under the moonlight ♫
♫ 月光下演奏西塔琴 ♫
♫ Drinks won’t let me forget ♫
♫ 饮料不会让我忘记 ♫
♫I write to you about my desire♫
♫我写给你的渴望♫
♫Our destiny is written on paper♫
♫我们的命运写在纸上♫
♫ Like the strongest wine ♫
♫ 就像最烈的酒♫
♫Destiny has no way out♫
♫命运没有出路♫
♫Looking back I see you waiting♫
♫回首我看到你在等待♫
♫Our life is very fulfilling♫
♫我们的生活很充实♫
♫Happiness and sadness♫
♫ 快乐与悲伤♫
♫ Desire crystallized♫
♫ 欲望结晶 ♫
♫ In the shining galaxy ♫
♫ 在闪亮的银河♫
♫ Please note, I play the sitar ♫
♫ 请注意，我弹西塔琴 ♫
♫Waiting for someone like you♫
♫等待像你这样的人♫
♫In the end you are my inevitable destiny♫
♫最终你 是我不可避免的命运♫
Does it hurt?
很痛吗？
Take it.
拿着它。
- Thanks. - This is our only medicine.
- 谢谢。 - 这是我们唯一的药。
Thanks.
谢谢。
thanks for your help.
感谢您的帮助。
This has nothing to do with helping.
这与帮助无关。
As an adult,
作为一个成年人，
Why are you like tofu?
你怎么像豆腐一样？
The slightest touch can hurt you.
最轻微的触摸都会伤害您。
You are more fragile than us girls.
你比我们女孩子还要脆弱。
Well, vulnerable, but able to dodge.
好吧，脆弱， 但能够躲闪。
When something so big flies
当这么大的东西飞起来的时候
Can't you see? You don't even know how to hide.
你看不见？ 你甚至不知道如何躲避。
I will deviate in the future.
未来我会偏离。
no future?
没有未来？
It doesn't matter.
不要紧。
You are still smiling.
你还在微笑。
Whenever I get angry and want to hit someone, you smile.
每当我生气 想打人的时候，你就微笑着。
Do you really know how to piss people off?
你真的知道如何激怒别人吗？
I smile because I'm happy.
我微笑是因为我很高兴。
As the young master of Xingxiang Pavilion,
作为星象阁的少主，
I need to smile.
我需要露出微笑。
Sometimes in order to appease people's hearts,
有时 为了安抚人心，
Sometimes, to put an end to evil,
有时，为了结束邪恶，
Rarely because of me.
很少因为我。
What's different from you is,
与你不同的是，
Who does what he wants.
谁做他想做的事。
you cry when you are sad
当你伤心的时候你会哭
Laugh when you are happy
开心的时候就笑
How you react if you are wronged
如果你受到委屈你会做出反应
you fight
你打架
For what you want.
为了你想要的。
meet people like you
见到像你这样的人
make me feel
使我感到
I still live in this mortal world.
我还活在这个凡人的世界里。
But the mortal world passed in an instant.
但红尘 转眼就过去了。
tonight,
今晚，
I am very happy,
我很高兴，
Really happy.
真的很高兴。
Do you remember the story I just told?
还记得我刚才讲的故事吗
About the previous emperor?
关于前任皇帝？
You say he is irresponsible.
你说他不负责任。
But, in my opinion,
但是，在我看来，
I do not think so.
我不这么认为。
He is Emperor Jialing,
他是嘉陵皇帝，
And married Jialin.
并为家琳结婚。
The only thing he did wrong
他唯一做错的事
That was the first time he saw her
那是他第一次见到她
At the age of 16,
16岁时，
he should back off
他应该退缩
and learn to let go,
并学会放手，
instead of persisting
而不是坚持下去
Without any consideration.
没有任何考虑。
like this,
像这样，
That person can continue
那人可以继续
An innocent and pure little girl,
一个天真纯洁的小女孩，
with a
与一个
different
不同的
But totally happy.
但完全高兴。
you mean
你的意思是
It's best for a person to be heartbroken
一个人最好是 心碎
Happier than both of them.
比两个人都不幸福。
Miss He, thank you for coming to see me off.
何小姐， 谢谢您前来送行。
us
我们
We must break up now.
我们现在必须分手了。
If I knew, I wouldn't give it to you...
如果我知道的话，我就不会给你...
Anyway, that's good.
无论如何，这很好。
No one's heart is broken
没有人心碎
Or unhappy.
或不高兴。
No one needs to grieve.
没有人需要悲伤。
I don't need this, you can stay.
我不需要这个，你可以留下来。
If you don't want it, you can throw it away.
如果你不想要它，你可以把它扔掉。
Thanks.
谢谢。
Rong Yu.
Rong Yu.
Don't be angry with me.
别生我的气。
I'll deviate next time.
下次我会偏离的。
You just said that.
你刚才就这么说了。
The lady is still alive.
那位女士还活着。
I remember how you stabbed me before.
我记得你之前是怎么刺伤我的。
Enemies meet.
敌人相遇。
Who are you?
你是谁？
Do you remember how I stabbed you?
你还记得我是怎么刺伤你的吗？
I wish I could do it again.
我希望我能再做一次。
Mate a Rong Yu.
Mate a Rong Yu.
leave. Don't touch him.
离开。不要碰他。
- Miss He. - Rong Yu, I just want to kill you,
- 何小姐。 - 容羽，我只是想杀了你，
But now you will have company in hell.
但现在你在地狱里会有同伴了。
You're going to hell.
你会下地狱的。
You talk too much. Watch me break your arm
你说得太多了。 看我折断你的手臂
Make your life worse than death.
让你生不如死。
Let her go.
放开她。
All you want is my life.
你想要的就是我的生活。
take.
采取。
Why would you trust them with your life?
你为什么要把你的生命交给他们？
- go to hell. ——He Jiuling.
- 去死吧。 ——何九龄。
- You bastard.
- 你这个混蛋。
I will kill you all.
我会杀掉你们所有人。
I made a mistake?
我犯了一个错误？
Did I do something wrong?
我做错什么了吗？
Or will it
或者会不会
Am I unable to escape the fate of becoming the loneliest star?
难道我就逃脱不了 成为最孤独的星星的命运了吗？
Even if I let go
就算我放手
the one i love
我爱的人
will leave me.
会离开我。
♫ Can’t wait for the night♫
♫ 等不及黑夜♫
♫ Flashing lights ♫
♫ 闪烁的灯光 ♫
♫Drink a cup of vicissitudes♫
♫喝一杯沧桑♫
♫I no longer have the impetuousness of my youth♫
♫我不再年轻时的浮躁♫
♫ Know that you are somewhere across the water♫
♫ 知道你在 水对岸的某个地方 ♫
♫I swim against the current♫
♫我逆流而行♫
♫ Let's drink to remember our sorrow ♫
♫ 让我们喝酒来纪念我们的悲伤♫
♫ A head full of white hair, laughing at troubled dreams ♫
♫ 满头白发， 笑苦恼的梦♫
[One month later]
[一个月后]
Speaking of the best young master in the family,
说起家林最好的少爷，
Unparalleled in appearance and intelligence,
他的外表 和智力都无与伦比，
Like a person who has been banished to immortality.
就像一个被谪仙的人。
Speaking of Star Master,
说到 夺星大师，
Although he possesses the power of heaven,
虽然他拥有通天之力，
He can't predict
他无法预测
your own destiny.
你自己的命运。
It’s easy to judge others but hard to judge yourself.
评判别人很容易， 但评判自己却很难。
This is completely tragic.
这完全是悲剧。
Just a month ago,
就在一个月前，
He was killed at Jianglingmen.
于江陵门被杀。
And he hasn't woken up yet.
而他还没有醒来。
Mr. Rong.
荣先生。
do you want to die
你想死吗
Or continue to suffer?
还是继续受苦？
Did you discover it?
你发现了吗？
If you still don't admit what you did to Rong Yu
如果你还不承认 自己对容羽做了什么
I will make your life a living hell.
我会把你的生活变成地狱。
Isn’t Xingxiang Pavilion destiny?
星象阁不是命运吗？
If I knew someone poisoned him
如果我知道 有人给他下毒
I don't need to do anything.
我不需要做任何事。
I've said it hundreds of times.
我已经说过几百次了。
I didn't poison him.
我没有毒害他。
I don’t know which brave hero he is
不知道是哪个勇敢的英雄
- did this nice thing for me. - you...
- 为我做了这件好事。 - 你...
Mr. Rong.
荣先生。
don't get your hands dirty
别弄脏你的手
and their sins.
和他们的罪恶。
What was the diagnosis given to Master Rong by the imperial physician?
太医给容少爷的诊断是什么？
All from the Imperial Medical Department
全部来自太医部
Right in Rong Mansion.
就在荣府之中。
But poison is a thing
但这毒是个东西
They had never seen or heard of it.
他们从未见过或听说过。
How should they solve it?
他们该如何解决呢？
According to my speculation,
根据我的推测，
The person who poisoned you could have been someone else.
给你下毒的人 可能是其他人。
Someone else?
另一个人？
How could there be anyone else?
怎么会有别人呢？
Who has such a big grudge against Rong Yu?
谁对容羽有这么大的恩怨
Want him to die?
要他死吗？
Jiuling.
Jiuling.
How is Jiuling?
九灵怎么样了？
We haven't told her about Rong Yu yet.
我们暂时还没有告诉她容羽的事。
Her body is still recovering.
她的身体还在恢复中。
That...
那...
your left hand...
你的左手...
Let me do it. I use monthly salary
让我来做吧。我用的是月工资
I also bought you beautiful hair accessories.
我还给你买了漂亮的发饰。
Aren't they beautiful?
她们不漂亮吗？
let's go,
我们走吧，
try it.
尝试一下。
Look how beautiful they are.
看看她们有多漂亮。
Don't tie all your hair into two braids.
不要把所有的头发都扎成两条辫子。
Doesn't look like a girl.
看起来不像个女孩。
Look how beautiful she is.
看看她多漂亮。
Otherwise they will think you are a boy.
不然他们会认为你是个男孩。
Jiuling, do you like them?
九龄，你喜欢他们吗？
He San.
何三.
I'm a little hungry. I'm going to find something to eat.
我有点饿了。 我去找点吃的。
group.
派。
brother.
兄弟。
What do you think the future will be like for Jiuling?
你觉得 九灵未来会怎样？
What a strong will.
多么坚强的意志啊。
How could she bear it?
她怎么能忍受？
It would be nice if I left...
要是我走了就好了……
A little before.
之前一点。
it's all my fault.
都是我的错。
So does my poor daughter.
我可怜的女儿也是这样。
E Rong Yu,
E Rong Yu,
I don't know when he will wake up.
我不知道他什么时候会醒来。
if he doesn't wake up
如果他不醒来的话
What will Ling do?
凌会做什么？
We'll have to wait and see.
我们必须拭目以待。
listen.
听。
you two,
你们俩，
Don't be sad when you see Ling.
当你看到凌时，不要难过。
If you feel bad, she will feel worse.
如果你感觉不好，她也会感觉更糟。
Mainly you.
主要是你。
I'm trying to cheer her up.
我正在努力让她高兴起来。
Today, I just can't take it anymore.
今天，我实在受不了了。
group.
派。
Maybe we should leave Wu Ritan
也许我们应该离开吴日坛
Take Ling for a walk.
带凌去散步。
Better than staying
总比留下来好
Trapped at home.
被困在家里。
Okay, looks great.
好吧，看起来很棒。
But we must remember her
但我们必须记住她
Not to mention Rong Yu
更不用说容钰了
In front of Ling.
凌面前。
Sim.
西姆。
What's wrong?
怎么了？
——Why did the young master faint? - I have no idea.
——少爷怎么会晕倒？ - 我不知道。
what happened?
发生了什么？
Why?
为什么？
Are there any signs that he's going to wake up?
有什么迹象表明他要醒来吗？
winter is very cold.
冬天很冷。
The cold air was trapped in his body,
冰冷的空气困在他的体内，
His pulse weakened again.
他的脉搏又变弱了。
Until we find a solution,
在我们找到解决方案之前，
I suggest taking the young master to the manor
我建议带少爷去庄园
With thermal water and geothermal heat.
与温泉水和地热。
Taking a hot spring bath every day can help improve your physical condition.
每天泡温泉， 有助于改善身体状况。
And survive the winter.
并度过冬天。
Thank you for your efforts.
谢谢你的努力。
Go home first.
先回家吧。
You don't need to come here every day.
你不需要每天都来这里。
Understood.
明白了。
Sim.
西姆。
Zhanping, Heshan.
Zhanping, Heshan.
Help him get dressed.
帮他穿好衣服。
Now let's go to the other mansion.
现在我们就去另一座宅邸吧。
Sim.
西姆。
here.
这里。
Miss He, if you are not satisfied,
何小姐，如果您不满意，
I have another piece.
我还有另一块。
This is a treasure that is not usually exposed. a while.
这是平时不会暴露出来的宝物。一会儿。
Is your whip bad?
你的鞭子不好吗？
Why should you consider changing weapons?
为什么要考虑换武器？
Not very good.
不是很好。
Weapons that have not tasted blood.
没有尝过血味的武器。
No matter how light or beautiful it is,
无论它多么轻盈或美丽，
If it's not to protect you, what's the point?
如果不是为了保护你，那 还有什么意义呢？
Miss He, take a look.
何小姐，你看一下。
A small dagger,
一把小匕首，
Compact, lightweight and convenient.
小巧、轻便、方便。
It is very suitable for girls.
它非常适合女孩。
Look, there are agates inlaid there.
看，那里镶嵌着玛瑙。
You can show it to other customers.
您可以将其展示给其他客户。
Miss He, what do you want?
何小姐，你想要什么？
- A sword.
- 一把剑。
Two types of 18 weapons,
两种18种武器，
Nine are long and nine are short. The blade is the best short weapon.
九个是长的，九个是短的。 刀刃是最好的短兵器。
In order to defeat the enemy and kill him, I need a knife.
为了打败敌人并杀死他， 我需要一把刀。
I'm very sorry.
我很抱歉。
In the weapons loft,
在武器阁楼中，
We mainly do business with young masters in Beijing.
我们主要是和京城的少爷做生意。
blade like weapon
像刀片一样的武器
It's just too vulgar.
实在是太庸俗了。
Miss He, take another look.
何小姐，你再看一下。
These are our top products.
这些是我们的顶级产品。
promise.
承诺。
But the blades can be heavy.
但刀片可能很重。
Use your hands...
用你的手...
I won't go on like this anymore.
我不会再这样下去了。
Maybe I won't lift it today,
也许今天我不会举起它，
But one day I will succeed.
但总有一天我会成功的。
Then help me choose a better weapon.
然后帮我选择更好的武器。
[Weapons Loft]
[武器阁楼]
Volt.
伏尔特。
- She is incapacitated. do not be afraid. - I'm not afraid.
- 她丧失了行动能力。不要害怕。 - 我不害怕。
I promised Master Rong not to mess with her.
我答应容少爷 不要惹她了。
Why make a deal with a loser?
为什么要和一个失败者做交易？
- Don't be a coward. let's go. - elder sister.
- 别做胆小鬼。我们走吧。 - 姐姐。
Jiuling.
Jiuling.
Put the tan down first.
先把棕褐色放下。
The grudge between us has nothing to do with her.
我们之间的恩怨 与她无关。
As long as you don't resist,
只要你不反抗，
I won't touch her.
我不会碰她。
If you're worried about what's going on in the palace
如果你担心 皇宫里发生的事情
Why don't you reflect on this?
你为什么不反思一下这一点呢？
Why is your mouth so dirty?
你的嘴怎么这么脏？
Given your circumstances, I admire your courage.
鉴于你的条件，我很佩服你的勇气。
Batanilla!
巴塔尼拉！
- No! -Jiu Ling. Let me go.
- 不！ -九龄。让我走。
- Do not move. - No.
- 不要动。 - 不。
——Nine spirits, nine spirits. - Do not move.
——九灵，九灵。 - 不要动。
- Stop hitting her. - Asshole.
- 别打她了 - 混蛋。
Don't touch Tan.
别碰谭。
Worry about yourself first.
先担心一下你自己吧。
Then take off all her clothes
然后脱掉她所有的衣服
and hang it on the market.
并将其挂在市场上。
I want to see if her mouth can handle it.
我倒要看看她的嘴还能不能承受得住。
Honor...
荣...
A Rong Yu.
A Rong Yu.
A Rong Yu?
A Rong Yu?
He could barely protect himself.
他几乎无法保护自己。
Do you think he can protect you every day?
你觉得他能 每天保护你吗？
What did you say?
你说什么？
He was injured, poisoned
他受伤了，中毒了
And has been in a coma for more than a month.
并且已经昏迷一个多月了。
You just got engaged to him
你刚刚和他订婚
That happened.
那件事发生了。
You are so unlucky.
你实在是太倒霉了。
What did you say?
你说什么？
Don't you understand our language?
你听不懂我们的语言吗？
Beat her. She had no medicine, no whip, and her hands were weak.
打她。她没有药，也没有鞭子， 她的手也无力了。
Are you still afraid of her?
你还怕她吗？
leave.
离开。
Come on, everyone.
大家都来吧。
break some bones
打断一些骨头
It's just going to cost me.
这只会让我付出代价。
if you break my bones
如果你打断我的骨头
I will give you my life.
我会给你我的生命。
You are not crazy. He is a mad dog.
你不是疯子。 他是一只疯狗。
Why don't you leave here?
你为什么不离开这里？
let's go.
我们走吧。
Jiuling.
Jiuling.
How could you be so stupid?
你怎么可以这么傻？
How are your hands?
你的手怎么样？
Tan.
谭。
take me Home.
带我回家。
I need to ask my dad something.
我需要问我父亲一些事情。
Doctor, be careful.
医生，仔细点。
I'm resetting her bones. How about it?
我正在重置她的骨头。 怎么样？
He San, I can handle it.
禾三，我能应付。
- Did you send someone to find dad? - I have sent.
- 你派人去找爸爸了吗？ - 我发了。
Be kind.
善待。
I said relax.
我说放轻松。
You wouldn't treat a man like that.
你不会对待一个男人。
Where is Rong Yu? Already awake? where is he?
容宇在哪里？ 已经醒了吗？他在哪里？
I'm not worried
我不烦恼
About Rong Yu.
关于容羽。
tell me,
告诉我，
Who did this to you?
谁对你做了这样的事？
I will avenge him.
我会为他报仇。
Was Rong Yu poisoned?
容羽中毒了吗？
I asked and everyone said no.
我问了，大家都说没有。
Father, tell me. I just want the truth.
父亲，你告诉我。我只想要真相。
I'm talking about your hands.
我说的是你的手。
My hands are fine.
我的手没问题。
I know,
我知道，
you all care about me
你们都关心我
But you are walking on thin ice
而你却如履薄冰
Worry about my hands.
担心我的手。
Even if my hand is injured, it's useless,
即使我的手 受伤了，没用，
I won't shed a single tear.
我不会流一滴眼泪。
but if
但如果
Rong Yu hasn’t woken up yet,
容玉还没有醒来，
What's more, my hands are useless,
更何况我的手是没用的，
I can die ten thousand times
我可以死一万次
No relief.
没有缓解。
Ling.
凌.
Ling, listen.
玲，听着。
Don't cry.
别哭。
Can you take care of the wound first?
你能先处理一下伤口吗？
Be good and listen to me.
乖一点，听我说。
I'll tell you later
我待会儿告诉你
all.
全部。
Whatever you want to know, okay?
不管你想知道什么，好吗？
good girl.
好女孩。
♫ When the sun sets at dusk♫
♫ 夕阳西下 黄昏时 ♫
♫I traveled thousands of miles♫
♫我旅行千里之外♫
♫ Play the sitar under the moonlight ♫
♫ 月光下演奏西塔琴 ♫
♫ Drinks won’t let me forget ♫
♫ 饮料不会让我忘记 ♫
♫I write to you about my desire♫
♫我写给你的渴望♫
♫Our destiny is written on paper♫
♫我们的命运写在纸上♫
♫ Like the strongest wine ♫
♫ 就像最烈的酒♫
♫ There is no escape from fate ♫
♫ 无法逃脱命运♫
♫Looking back I see you waiting♫
♫回首我看到你在等待♫
♫Our lives are full of joy and sadness♫
♫我们的生活充满 欢乐和悲伤♫
♫ Desire crystallizes into shining stars♫
♫ 欲望结晶 成闪亮的星系♫
♫ You turn around silently and close the wedding book♫
♫ 你默默转身 ，合上结婚簿♫
♫Ask how many stars there are in the sky♫
♫问天上有多少颗星星♫
♫I write to you about my desire♫
♫我写给你的渴望♫
♫Our destiny is written on paper♫
♫我们的命运写在纸上♫
♫ Like the strongest wine ♫
♫ 就像最烈的酒♫
♫ There is no escape from fate ♫
♫ 无法逃脱命运♫
♫Looking back I see you waiting♫
♫回首我看到你在等待♫
♫Our lives are full of joy and sadness♫
♫我们的生活充满 欢乐和悲伤♫
♫ Desire crystallizes into shining stars♫
♫ 欲望结晶 成闪亮的星系♫
♫I play the sitar softly waiting for someone like you♫
♫我轻轻地弹奏西塔琴 等待像你这样的人♫
♫In the end you are my inevitable destiny♫
♫最终你 是我不可避免的命运♫